( phone ringing )
HELLO.
HEY, JOEY.
Hey, Pheebs.
LISTEN, CAN YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
I FORGOT THE PIN NUMBER
TO MY ATM CARD.
CAN YOU GET IT FOR ME?
Sure. Where is it?
I SCRATCHED IT ON THE ATM
MACHINE DOWN ON THE CORNER.
OH, SO YOU'RE 5639?
THAT'S IT. THANKS, PHEEBS.
HEY.
OH, DO YOU WANT
TO TALK TO CHANDLER?
IS THAT JOEY?
LET ME TALK TO HIM.
No, 'cause he didn't
believe in my movie
WHICH IS A BIG MISTAKE,
BECAUSE IT IS REAL. REAL.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO APOLOGIZE
TO HIM ALL WEEK.
IF HE'S NOT GOING TO LET ME
DO IT ON THE PHONE
I'M GOING DOWN THERE,
I'M GOING TO DO IT IN PERSON.
PHEEBS, I HEARD THAT.
CAN YOU PUT HIM ON?
YEAH.
HEY.
DON'T COME OUT HERE.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I SUPPORT YOU 100%
AND I WANT TO PROVE THAT
TO YOU IN PERSON.
I GOT THAT. I FORGIVE YOU.
DON'T COME OUT HERE.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN TAKING MY CALLS
FOR A WEEK.
I'M TOTALLY OVER IT, CHANDLER.
FRIENDS FOREVER.
DON'T COME OUT HERE.
WOULD YOU MIND
DOING A PICTURE WITH US?
WHAT WAS THAT?
UH, ENTERTAINMENT TONIGHT.
Yeah. Okay, so...
GOOD TALKING TO YOU,
AND DON'T COME OUT HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
MONICA?
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
PHOEBE?
OH, PHOEBE I'M SO SORRY.
HAVE YOU BEEN HERE LONG?
THAT'S OKAY.
WHAT THE HELL
TOOK YOU SO LONG?
OKAY, YOU CANNOT
TELL CHANDLER, OKAY?
BUT I RAN INTO RICHARD.
WHICH RICHARD?
THE RICHARD.
RICHARD SIMMONS?
OH, MY GOD.
NO. MY EX-BOYFRIEND, RICHARD.
YOU KNOW, THE TALL GUY,
MUSTACHE?
OH, OKAY. THAT ACTUALLY
MAKES MORE SENSE.
SO HOW WAS IT?
IT WAS REALLY NICE.
WE STARTED TALKING
AND THEN I-I ENDED UP
HAVING LUNCH WITH HIM.
THAT IS SO WEIRD.
I HAD A DREAM
THAT YOU HAD LUNCH
WITH RICHARD.
REALLY?
BUT AGAIN, RICHARD SIMMONS.
GO ON.
THE STRANGE PART WAS,
HE WAS REALLY NICE
AND HE LOOKS GREAT
BUT I DIDN'T FEEL
ANYTHING AT ALL.
OOH. SO NOW, WHY CAN'T
WE TELL CHANDLER?
BECAUSE IT'LL
TOTALLY FREAK HIM OUT.
TOMORROW'S OUR ANNIVERSARY.
I JUST DON'T WANT
ANYTHING TO SPOIL THAT.
OH. I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS
HAVE LASTED A WHOLE YEAR.
WOW, I OWE RACHEL
20 BUCKS.
WHAT?
ON A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT BET.
HEY.
IT'S ALMOST OUR ANNIVERSARY.
I KNOW.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
ONE YEAR AGO TODAY
I WAS JUST YOUR
ANNOYING FRIEND, CHANDLER.
AW... NOW YOU'RE JUST
MY ANNOYING FRIEND, CHANDLER.
HUH.
I GOT YOU A PRESENT.
OH, BUT IT'S
NOT TILL TOMORROW.
I KNOW, BUT YOU HAVE
TO OPEN IT TODAY.
OKAY.
( both tittering )
( tittering )
OKAY! THERE YOU GO!
IT'S TWO TICKETS TO VEGAS!
WOW!
YEAH, FOR THIS WEEKEND!
OH, GOSH, IT'LL BE PERFECT.
YOU GET TO SEE JOEY.
PLUS, WE GET TO START
OUR ANNIVERSARY CELEBRATION
ON THE PLANE.
WE CAN CALL IT
OUR "PLANE-IVERSARY."
DO WE HAVE TO?
NO.
OKAY, BUT THIS IS GREAT,
BUT JOEY SAID HE DIDN'T WANT
ANY OF US OUT THERE.
OH, HE JUST DOESN'T WANT US
TO GO THROUGH ANY TROUBLE.
THINK HOW EXCITED
HE'S GOING TO BE
WHEN WE GO
AND SURPRISE HIM.
PLUS, WE GET TO HAVE
OUR OWN...
"ANNI-VEGAS-RY."
"AN-NEVADA-VERSARY"!
YEAH, I THINK WE SHOULD
SEE OTHER PEOPLE.
BUT WE CAN GO, RIGHT?
YES.
OKAY.
IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
OKAY, I'M GOING
TO GO, TOO.
YOU KNOW, PHEEBS, IT'S
KIND OF OUR ANNIVERSARY.
PLEASE. YOU ARE NOT
GOING TO DITCH ME AGAIN
LIKE YOU DID WITH LONDON.
DITCH YOU? PHOEBE,
YOU WERE PREGNANT WITH...
UH-HUH, GREAT STORY.
I'M GOING.
HI.
Phoebe: HEY.
HEY, YOU GUYS, LISTEN.
THIS WEEKEND WE'RE ALL
GOING TO GO TO LAS VEGAS
TO SURPRISE JOEY--
INCLUDING ME!
DO YOU WANT TO GO?
WELL, I GUESS I COULD TAKE
A COUPLE DAYS OFF WORK.
OF COURSE YOU COULD TAKE
A COUPLE DAYS OFF WORK
BECAUSE THIS TRIP INCLUDES ME!
OH, NO. WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT. I'VE GOT
A PRESENTATION TOMORROW.
I CAN'T MISS THAT.
OH, I'VE GOT TICKETS
TO THE VAN GOGH EXHIBIT.
I'VE BEEN WAITING, LIKE,
A YEAR FOR THIS.
SO, RACH, WHY DON'T YOU AND I
FLY OUT TOGETHER SATURDAY?
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I'LL CALL THE AIRLINES.
OKAY. YEAH.
THAT'LL BE NICE, ACTUALLY
TO HAVE THE APARTMENT
TO MYSELF FOR A NIGHT.
OH, YEAH, SO YOU CAN
WALK AROUND NAKED.
NO. SO I CAN BE BY MYSELF.
YOU KNOW,
HAVE A LITTLE ALONE TIME.
YEAH, NAKED ALONE TIME.
NO, PHOEBE. JUST BECAUSE
I'M ALONE DOESN'T MEAN
I WANT TO WALK
AROUND NAKED.
I MEAN, YOU LIVE ALONE.
YOU DON'T WALK AROUND NAKED.
UH-HUH. WHY DO YOU THINK
IT TAKES ME SO LONG
TO ANSWER THE DOOR?
SO, SO FAR, IS THIS TRIP
TO LAS VEGAS BETTER OR WORSE
THAN THE TRIP TO LONDON?
SO FAR, IT'S PRETTY MUCH
THE SAME, PHEEBS.
OKAY. WHAT ABOUT AFTER
I GIVE YOU THESE CANDIES?
YEAH, I GUESS IT'S
A LITTLE BETTER NOW.
HA-HA.
OKAY, LAS VEGAS-- ONE;
LONDON-- ZERO.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK. OOH.
HAPPY "PLANE-IVERSARY."
AW... I LOVE YOU.
CAN I GIVE YOU
YOUR PRESENT NOW?
OKAY.
OH, MAN. DON'T
TELL ME I DID THIS.
I LOVE "I FORGOT
THE PRESENT" FAKE OUT!
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
THE "I REALLY DID
FORGET THE PRESENT
PLEASE FORGIVE ME"
NOT FAKE OUT?
HONEY, THAT'S OKAY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU CAN GIVE IT TO ME
WHEN WE GET BACK.
NO, THIS IS THE WORST THING
THAT CAN HAPPEN ON
AN ANNIVERSARY EVER.
OH, GOOD, ALL RIGHT.
YOU DECIDED TO TELL HIM
ABOUT THE RICHARD THING.
WHAT... WHAT
"RICHARD THING"?
OH, NO.
WHAT "RICHARD THING"?
SIMMONS. GO WITH SIMMONS.
OKAY. I, UM... I RAN
INTO RICHARD YESTERDAY
AND HE ASKED ME IF I WANTED
TO GO FOR A BITE AND I DID.
THE ONLY REASON WHY
I DIDN'T TELL YOU IS BECAUSE
I-I KNEW YOU'D GET MAD
AND I DIDN'T WANT
TO SPOIL OUR ANNIVERSARY.
I'M NOT MAD.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, SO YOU BUMPED
INTO RICHARD.
YOU GRABBED A BITE.
NO BIG DEAL.
GREAT.
OKAY, LONDON-- ONE.
OOH!
HMM.
( gasps )
OH, LOOK WHAT HAPPENED.
HA, CHECK ME OUT.
I'M IN MY KITCHEN... NAKED.
I'M PICKING UP AN ORANGE.
I'M NAKED.
LIGHTING THE CANDLES NAKED
AND CAREFULLY...
OH, MY GOD,
THAT'S RACHEL NAKED!
I CAN'T LOOK AT THAT.
I AM LOOKING AT THIS.
OKAY, VIVID COLORS,
EXPRESSIVE BRUSH STROKES...
UNLESS SHE WANTS ME
TO BE LOOKING AT THAT.
SHE KNOWS I'M HOME.
SHE KNOWS I CAN SEE HER.
WHAT KIND OF GAME
IS SHE PLAYING?
I THINK MAYBE
SOMEONE'S LONELY TONIGHT.
( chuckling ):
OH, DR. GELLER, STOP IT.
YOU'RE BEING SILLY.
( chuckles )
OR AM I?
♪ I... love to love you, baby ♪
OW!
OW.
( knock on door )
♪ I... love to love you, baby ♪
( music stops )
♪ MMM...
LOVE TO LOVE YOU, BABY ♪
OW. DARN IT.
( groans )
HEY.
MAY I COME IN?
UH, YEAH, IF YOU WANT TO.
DO YOU WANT ME TO?
YEAH, SURE?
SO DO I.
OKAY, RACH, BEFORE
ANYTHING HAPPENS
I JUST WANT TO LAY DOWN
A COUPLE OF GROUND RULES.
THIS IS JUST ABOUT TONIGHT.
I DON'T WANT
TO GO THROUGH WITH THIS
IF IT'S GOING TO RAISE
THE QUESTION OF "US."
OKAY? I JUST WANT
THIS TO BE...
( shoe thumps )
ABOUT WHAT IT IS.
AND, UM...
( clearing throat )
W-WHAT IS THAT, ROSS?
THE PHYSICAL ACT OF LOVE.
WHAT? ARE YOU CRAZY?
OH, SO-SO YOU WEREN'T TRYING
TO ENTICE ME JUST NOW
WITH YOUR, YOUR NAKEDNESS?
( gasps )
OH... GOD.
YOU SAW ME?
OH...
YOU WEREN'T TRYING TO ENTICE ME
WITH YOUR NAKEDNESS.
NO, NO.
YOU THOUGHT...
YOU ACTUALLY THOUGHT
I WANTED TO HAVE SEX WITH YOU?
OH, MY...
NO.
NO... NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
♪ MONEY, MONEY, MONEY, MONEY ♪
♪ MONEY ♪
HEY, YOU GUYS... WAIT.
YOU GUYS, THIS PLACE IS SO MUCH
BETTER THAN LONDON, OKAY?
THIS LADY DRESSED
LIKE CLEOPATRA
GAVE ME THIS COUPON--
99-CENT STEAK
AND LOBSTER DINNER. HUH.
PHOEBE, YOU DON'T
EAT ANIMALS.
FOR 99 CENTS,
I'D EAT YOU.
OKAY. I COULD TOTALLY
SETTLE DOWN HERE.
IT'S GOT EVERYTHING
I COULD EVER WANT.
INCLUDING JOEY. LOOK!
OH, LOOK. HI!
OH, MY GOD.
HEY, JOEY!
HEY! HEY!
WOW.
HI.
LOVE YOUR CONDOMS, MY MAN.
W-WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
DOING HERE?
I-I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
NOT TO COME.
WHY ARE YOU DRESSED
AS A GLADIATOR?
UH... BECAUSE...
I'M SHOOTING
A SCENE RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, I, UH...
I PLAY A GLADIATOR.
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
HOLD ON A SECOND.
CAN WE CUT?!
YEAH, MY-MY FRIENDS ARE HERE.
I'M GOING TO TAKE
A LITTLE BREAK.
WHO-WHO ARE YOU
TALKING TO?
THE, UH...
DIRECTOR.
UH... HER.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
IT'S NOT A GLADIATOR MOVIE.
I WORK HERE.
WHY? WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, THE MOVIE
GOT SHUT DOWN
BECAUSE THEY RAN
OUT OF MONEY
SO I'M WORKING HERE
TILL IT STARTS UP AGAIN
IF IT EVER DOES.
OH, SUCH A DRAG.
LOOK, I'M SORRY
I DIDN'T TELL YOU.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
NO, NO, IT'S OKAY.
APPARENTLY THERE'S
A NEW POLICY
WHERE WE DON'T HAVE TO SHARE
EVERYTHING WITH EVERYBODY.
I KNEW YOU WERE NOT
OKAY WITH THAT.
SO YOU'RE A GLADIATOR?
YEAH, WHAT'S
GOING ON?
MONICA HAD
LUNCH WITH RICHARD.
DAWSON?
Phoebe:
NO...
BUT THAT WOULD
HAVE BEEN SO COOL.
NO, HER BOYFRIEND, RICHARD.
IT MEANT NOTHING, OKAY?
AFTER ALL THIS TIME,
HOW CAN YOU NOT TRUST ME?
WHEN YOU GO LUNCHING
WITH HUNKY MUSTACHE MEN
AND DON'T TELL ME ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M SORRY,
I SHOULD HAVE TOLD YOU.
THANKS.
AW, THERE WE GO.
I LOVE VEGAS.
I PROMISE YOU,
NEXT TIME
I ABSOLUTELY
WILL TELL YOU.
NEXT TIME?
OOH, SO CLOSE.
THERE'S NOT GOING
TO BE A NEXT TIME.
YOU CANNOT SEE HIM
EVER AGAIN.
I CANNOT SEE HIM?
I MEAN, YOU CAN'T
TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
OH, THAT'S SO FUNNY,
BECAUSE I THINK I JUST DID.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE
ACTING LIKE THIS ALL NIGHT
I DON'T EVEN WANT
TO BE AROUND YOU.
FINE WITH ME.
FINE. HAPPY ANNIVERSARY.
WHOA, GUYS, GUYS, PLEASE.
COME ON, THIS IS OBVIOUSLY
JUST A BIG
MISUNDERSTANDING.
NO, IT IS NOT.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HEY, HEY!
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I JUST WORK HERE.
OKAY, UM... ROSS?
I'M A LITTLE WARM
SO I'M GOING TO BE
TAKING OFF MY SWEATER.
NOW, I'M, I'M JUST
LETTING YOU KNOW
THIS IS NOT
AN INVITATION
TO THE PHYSICAL
ACT OF LOVE.
YEP, THAT'S HILARIOUS.
I'M SORRY,
I'M DONE. I'M DONE.
YOU KNOW, LAST NIGHT
WAS EMBARRASSING
FOR YOU, TOO.
NO, NOT REALLY.
I JUST DON'T
EMBARRASS THAT EASILY.
WHAT? YOU TOTALLY
GET EMBARRASSED.
NO, I DON'T.
ROSS, I THINK I'M JUST
A MORE SECURE PERSON
THAN YOU ARE.
IS THAT SO?
YEAH.
HEY, LADY!
I DON'T CARE
HOW MUCH YOU WANT IT, OKAY?!
I AM NOT GOING
TO HAVE SEX WITH YOU
IN THE BATHROOM!
HEY, YOU KNOW,
IN ROMAN TIMES
THIS WAS MORE
THAN JUST A HAT.
REALLY?
YEAH, SURE, SURE.
THEY WOULD SCRUB
THE FLOORS WITH IT.
THEY WOULD USE IT TO GET
THE MUD OFF THEIR SHOE
AND SOMETIMES, UNDERNEATH
THE HORSE WOULD GET DIRTY
SO THEY WOULD STICK IT...
JOEY!
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS IS HOW
I'M SPENDING MY ANNIVERSARY.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TAKE
YOU SOMEPLACE NICE THEN.
LOOK. A GUY TIPPED ME
100 BUCKS TODAY.
WHOA.
YEAH, YEAH.
HE WAS PLAYING BLACKJACK
FOR LIKE AN HOUR
AND HE WON $5,000.
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT? $5,000.
YOU KNOW, IF I WON $5,000,
I'D JOIN A GYM.
YOU KNOW,
BUILD UP MY UPPER BODY
AND HIT RICHARD
FROM BEHIND WITH A STICK.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHY DON'T I JUST DO
WHAT THAT GUY DID?
I'LL TAKE THIS $100,
TURN IT INTO $5,000
AND THEN I'LL TURN THAT
INTO ENOUGH MONEY
TO GET MY MOVIE
GOING AGAIN.
GOOD LUCK.
CHANDLER,
I DON'T NEED LUCK.
I HAVE THOUGHT THIS THROUGH.
I SEE.
THANK YOU.
THANKS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
THIS IS LIKE THE
WORST NIGHT EVER.
YOU KNOW, MONICA,
YOU HAD A MINOR SETBACK
IN YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH CHANDLER.
BIG DEAL.
IT'S ONLY CHANDLER.
I AM SO SORRY.
THIS IS CRAZY.
I MEAN, IT WAS SUCH
A STUPID ARGUMENT.
I DIDN'T EVEN WANT
TO SEE RICHARD AGAIN.
SO GO FIX IT.
GO FIND CHANDLER.
HE'S PROBABLY UP
IN YOUR ROOM.
TELL HIM THAT YOU'RE SORRY
AND THAT YOU LOVE HIM.
YOU'RE RIGHT, PHOEBE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
SURE.
YEAH! LAS VEGAS--
NUMBER ONE!
DID ANYBODY LOSE THIS?
COMING OUT.
PLACE YOUR BETS.
DICE ARE OUT.
YO, 11.
PAY THE FRONT LINE.
HMM.
SO, UH...
I'M ON MY WAY BACK
TO THE BATHROOM.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
JUST KEEP WALKING, ALL RIGHT?
( chortling )
ROSS, WHAT ARE YOU...?
I'M SORRY, SIR.
I THINK HE JUST
REALLY LIKES YOU.
HEY, YOU KNOW
THAT TEACHER WHO HAD
A BABY WITH HER STUDENT?
( humming tune )
WHAT THE?!
HI.
MAY I HELP YOU?
YES, I'M SORRY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY
EXTRA PANTS?
MY FRIEND SEEMS TO HAVE
HAD A LITTLE "ACCIDENT."
CAN I CHANGE $100?
CHANGING $100.
GOOD LUCK, SIR.
THANKS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THIRTEEN.
HIT ME.
OH, MAN!
WAIT.
CHANDLER, YOU ARE NOT
GOING TO BELIEVE THIS.
I HAVE FOUND
MY IDENTICAL HAND TWIN.
WHAT?
WHAT'S AN IDENTICAL
HAND TWIN?
IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
CHANDLER, THE DEALER'S HANDS
WERE EXACTLY LIKE MINE.
IT WAS LIKE LOOKING
AT MY HANDS IN A MIRROR.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU WEREN'T
LOOKING AT YOUR
HANDS IN A MIRROR?
DON'T YOU SEE
WHAT THIS MEANS?
I CAN FORGET ABOUT
THAT STUPID MOVIE.
I'M GOING TO BE
A MILLIONAIRE!
HOW?
LOOK, I DON'T HAVE IT
ALL WORKED OUT YET
BUT IT'S GOT TO MEAN
BIG MONEY.
COME ON, IDENTICAL HANDS.
AGAIN I MUST GO BACK TO...
HOW?
THIS IS VEGAS, MAN.
PEOPLE WILL PAY TO SEE
FREAKY STUFF.
HOW MUCH WOULD YOU PAY
TO SEE THIS HAND...
TWICE?
HUH?
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T REALLY
PUT A PRICE ON THAT, JOE.
HEY, ARE YOU UNSUPPORTING
ME AGAIN?
NO, NO.
I SUPPORT YOU 100%.
I JUST DIDN'T... I DIDN'T
GET IT RIGHT AWAY.
NOW I'M CAUGHT UP.
IDENTICAL HAND TWINS.
IT'S A MILLION-DOLLAR IDEA.
RIGHT?
( knocking )
HEY.
PHEEBS...
YEAH?
I FOUND MY IDENTICAL
HAND TWIN!
OH, YOU'RE SO LUCKY.
HEY.
SO, WHERE'S MONICA?
DID YOU GUYS MAKE UP?
NO.
BUT SHE JUST
CAME UP HERE.
THAT WAS JOEY.
I WONDER WHERE SHE IS.
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
YEAH, WELL, SHE'S PROBABLY
TALKING TO RICHARD.
WOULD YOU STOP THAT?
YOU WANT TO KNOW
THE FIRST THING SHE SAID
WHEN SHE CAME BACK FROM
HER LUNCH WITH RICHARD?
SHE DIDN'T FEEL
ANYTHING FOR HIM.
SHE LOVES YOU.
REALLY?
YES.
SHE FEELS TERRIBLE.
SHE REALLY WANTS TO MAKE UP.
YOU'VE GOT TO FIND HER.
OKAY.
GOOD.
I SHOULD REALLY START
WEARING HATS.
YAY!
YES! YES!
COME ON!
WHERE ARE THE DICE?
WELCOME TO LAS VEGAS.
DID YOU ENJOY...
YOUR FLIGHT?
YES, I DID.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT WAS EXCELLENT.
HOPE YOU HAD
A NICE FLIGHT.
OH, IT WAS THE BEST.